OUR STICKY LOVE
The clumsy kiss…
Forget it.
This one's for real.
I don't get why people say that even rags
can look designer on a great body.
It takes hard work to get a great body.
Why dress yourself in rags?
DETECTIVE AGENCY
-Yes?
-We found a patient named Go Ji-won.
In her early thirties.
Admitted two weeks ago.
She's at a university hospital
in Gyeongbuk.
Are you sure the patient is Go Ji-won?
Tell me the hospital's location.
You go first.
You stopped crying.
You made me stop crying.
Yeah.
If that was your goal, you succeeded.
That's a relief.
That doesn't make it okay.
Though I guess
I did the same thing yesterday.
So I'll just call it even.
Don't ever do that again.
-Why not?
-Huh?
What I meant to say was…
When you've lived together for two years,
you're bound to bump lips all the time.
you do this all the time.
-Some days, it gets intense.
-Some days, it gets pretty intense.
And some days, it won't end…
And some days,
it doesn't end with just this.
You must be completely insane!
You pretended to be such a gentleman,
but all men are the same.
There's no chance,
so don't even dream about it.
Let's go home.
Excuse me?
You want to take me home?
Then will you live out here?
Eat up.
I heard you didn't eat much today.
I guess you do know
a thing or two about me.
Eat some rice too.
You need a balanced diet
to recover quickly.
Carbs make you gain weight.
It doesn't matter. You'll still be pretty.
This one's cooked.
Aren't you going to eat?
I'm full.
Just eat.
You think I'd be grateful if you said
you were full just watching me eat?
but then have my leftovers?
I really am full.
I had Chinese food earlier.
What?
It's just,
I didn't know you could smile.
I liked you from the moment I saw you.
This one's for real.
Why did he have to wear a suit today?
I wouldn't have flinched
if he was in that scrappy boxer outfit.
I couldn't stop thinking about you.
I just hoped…
to see you again someday.
Seeing you hurt was unbearable.
It killed me.
You're the only woman I've ever liked,
so I don't really know how.
If that look in his eyes was an act,
then he deserves a best actor award.
So he really is my boyfriend?
Then what was that with the toad?
It didn't scare me at all.
I guess you lost your fear
with your memory.
The doctor said head injuries
can cause all sorts of aftereffects.
Is that really it?
Did I simply change?
Oh my, Eun-sae?
Go Eun-sae, what's wrong with you?
If you can't wrap your head around it,
you don't have to.
You don't have to believe it.
Don't let those butterflies fool you.
Are you sure the patient is Go Ji-won?
Tell me the hospital's location.
He definitely said "patient"
and "hospital."
The fact that he's scouring hospitals
to find Go Eun-sae
means he thinks she's alive
and doesn't know
Baek Sang-gil dealt with her.
She had these on her.
That man is Mayor Ju's aide.
He went undercover
to gather information on the prosecution.
He's one of us,
so you don't have to worry about him.
The undercover agent is acting on his own.
But why?
How did he know to come here?
KAITO
Hey. Any progress?
We have the stowaway boat's
departure date.
Good work.
Make sure the information doesn't leak.
HONG'S BOXING GYM
What the hell?
I thought he was a mole,
not her real boyfriend.
Why would he be looking for Prosecutor Go?
What's more important
is that he knows about Taffy Village.
I thought this place was safe
and hard to track down, so how…
Hold on.
You said he's been searching hospitals?
What does he look like?
That's him. This guy came here yesterday.
What?
-Are you the head coach here?
-He asked if I was the head coach.
Did you happen to visit
a hospital yesterday?
Then asked if I'd visited the hospital.
You know,
since he's managed to track her here,
how about telling Prosecutor Go the truth?
I slept like a baby.
My gosh! Why did I sleep in so late?
What's up with you, Eun-sae?
You shouldn't be sleeping
so soundly already.
You should still be suspicious
that all of this might not be true.
We can't just wait around forever
for her memory to come back.
She's suspicious anyway.
Let's just tell her everything.
Tell her that Baek Sang-gil
is no ordinary guy,
so if she wants to stay alive,
she should leave Korea right away.
Let's persuade her like that.
We can't.
Why not?
If she hears all that without her memory,
she'll try to verify it for herself.
Whether she's really a prosecutor.
Whether I'm lying.
She'd try to get to the bottom of it.
She'd be in even more danger.
We could just stop her from doing that.
If someone has no memory of being burned,
no amount of warning
will make them fear fire.
They need to remember
how hot and scary fire is
to know how to avoid it.
Fair enough.
She still doesn't believe you,
so even if we tell her all this
and insist she has to leave Korea now,
I doubt she'd just say "Okay,"
and agree to leave.
Goodness.
I guess we need her memory back fast.
We're running out of time.
Kaito called and told me
the stowaway boat leaves in a month.
She needs her memory back before then.
Don't we need to do something
about that mole boyfriend?
He even knows about Taffy Village.
Shouldn't we at least distract him?
Baek Sang-gil could keep him at bay
faster and more effectively.
He'd also want to stop anyone
poking around to find Prosecutor Go.
Do you have a plan?
Sending you the detective agency's number.
You were asked
to find someone recently, right?
I'll give you a much easier job
and pay triple the agreed amount.
How childish.
What's with the apples?
BREAKFAST, LUNCH, DINNER
What am I, a kid? Ridiculous.
What are you doing here
so bright and early?
I just…
The reading fee.
Reading fee?
About yesterday…
I was wrong.
It felt like you were insulting my spirit,
and you were so rude and disrespectful,
so I just stood my ground.
I'd rather not receive payment
from a customer who isn't satisfied.
It just doesn't feel right.
Well,
you got there in the end.
That's good.
I'm saying this because
I thought I'd be the bigger person,
even though I really can't stand you…
Come on. Where's this going?
I'm sorry.
-What?
-I said I'm sorry.
As an elder, I shouldn't be fighting
someone who's so much younger than me.
I wasn't at my best.
Well, I also…
apologize for my behavior.
Gosh, you even know how
to lower your head?
When did I lower my head?
Then what was that damn bow?
Or did your neck take over?
"Damn"? Are you here to pick a fight
or apologize? Which is it?
A mix of both. So what?
Thanks for giving this back.
You can leave if that's all.
Don't you worry.
I'll leave even if you beg me not to.
Madam Shaman.
I'm giving you this because I also thought
I'd be the bigger person,
even though I can't stand you.
Absolutely ridiculous.
Well, I guess she is an elder.
She looked like
she'd never back down yesterday.
What's gotten into her?
Hey, I apologized just now.
I even gave back the fee because I felt
uneasy about accepting your money.
I've been downing cups of ice-cold water,
but I'm still fuming inside.
Tae-ha, you should really reconsider.
If you take in a woman like that
as your wife,
your life could go up in smoke.
-This should be enough.
-What are you doing?
For the broken Bodhisattva statue.
-How can you…
-Please accept it.
I'm sorry.
And please apologize to Eun-sae.
Instead of bringing her here
to apologize to me,
you want me to go
and apologize to that brat?
I heard that you grabbed her hair.
-But--
-That's assault.
Well, that was--
You frowned on my becoming a thug.
You despise violence,
yet you resorted to it.
So please apologize.
What about her disrespecting her elders
without knowing her place?
If you apologize first as her elder,
she'll follow suit.
Right, I'm sure
that brat would do just that.
I'm certain she will.
She's just not in her right mind
following the accident.
She's a good person.
Do you look at people with a blindfold on?
How can you be
such a bad judge of character?
I know that
you're also a good person.
What's that now?
I still remember
how you'd give me rice cakes
whenever you ran into me
on my way home from school.
And how you used to stuff my pockets
with boiled eggs,
saying that athletes shouldn't go hungry.
Thanks to you, I was a good athlete.
Thank you.
Why are you saying all that now?
You're saying whatever for your girl.
I'd really appreciate it.
What about dinner?
Have you eaten?
I made some red bean rice cakes
last night.
I'll pack some up.
Since I have this,
I guess I could color it in.
Eat breakfast, done
Eat dinner, done
When I opened the window…
You're up.
I've been up for a while.
It's not like the bed is comfortable.
That shaman lady came by earlier.
She did?
She apologized and even paid me back.
That's good.
I guess I'm not the type
to be hated for long.
If you're done eating, let's go.
Where to?
The clinic you went to yesterday.
You need treatment
to get your memory back fast.
Get ready.
What was that? If this is all a lie,
shouldn't he be hoping
I don't regain my memory?
Then why is he so eager to help me
get my memory back?
Is he really my boyfriend?
Why don't you try selling stuff
on Instagram too?
I bet you could get followers
and become an influencer in no time.
No, I couldn't.
Have you forgotten who you are?
You're the legendary Min Su-ji
who ruled beauty forums back in the day.
Right, Dr. An?
Yeah, back in the day.
I'm going to go brush my teeth.
Hey, can we talk…
How long will you keep this up?
I told you that I had no choice
but to go on that blind date.
I told you that my parents and I
run on give-and-take.
They set up this clinic for me,
so I have to follow their wishes somewhat.
I kept refusing until now,
and I only went on one date.
Exactly.
What?
You kept refusing, but you never told them
that you have a girlfriend.
That's because--
At the clinic and with your parents,
you always hide me.
You say it's because of what the staff
or your parents might say,
but the truth is,
I'm just not good enough for you, am I?
-How could you say--
-Not some nurse's aide.
You want to meet a woman
fit for a clinic director, don't you?
Then what about you?
If you felt that way,
why are you still with me?
It's because I own a clinic, isn't it?
-So I've decided to know my place.
-What's that supposed to mean?
I'm saying we should break up.
You're free to go on those blind dates.
I'll find a man who's more on my level.
Hey, Min Su-ji.
-Su-ji.
-Hello.
This is the director.
Here. I brought him.
Someone to vouch for my identity.
Nice to meet you.
What's with the "nice to meet you"?
-He said you were classmates.
-Classmates?
Long time no see, Jang Tae-ha.
All right, 1,000 won for a round!
Come play balloon toss!
-Wow, Min Su-ji is so pretty.
-No wonder she's Internet famous.
Wow, she's a goddess.
The "it" girl of Gujin.
She's glowing.
AN GI-JUN
Get your makeup done here!
Here's your yulmu tea.
Thanks. I just love yulmu tea.
It's boiling today.
Should we get drinks? Cola?
-Cola sounds good.
-Sure.
Hey, can we get three colas?
Sure.
Wipe your sweat with this.
Thanks.
What was your name again?
Su… Sun-deok?
That would be me.
It's Su-ji. Min Su-ji.
Of course. Thanks, Min Su-ji.
DIRECTOR AN GI-JUN
Oh, come on.
Our nurses are so clumsy.
Can I take a card?
Sure, please do.
Looking at this, I think I remember.
Weren't you the guy
who always got the best grades?
Well, not always.
You were so smart,
and now you're a doctor.
And how are you doing these days?
I heard you got into something else
after you gave up boxing.
I left that job recently.
I see.
Ms. Go Eun-sae told me
about her situation.
But our hospital has regulations.
-If a person's unverified, we can't--
-Thanks.
You'll treat her, won't you?
Otherwise, you wouldn't have called.
Right, yeah.
I'll pay whatever it costs,
so please do what you can for her.
Okay.
-It's a good thing I'm the director--
-Exactly.
So these are the perks
of having a capable classmate.
Thanks in advance.
Yeah, sure.
What are they talking about for so long?
You're beautiful.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I'm sorry, but…
I do. I'm sorry.
Understood. My apologies.
Here you go.
It's okay.
I only drink coffee
that's been freshly roasted.
-How did it go?
-You'll come twice a week for treatment.
Really?
Ms. Go Eun-sae, we'll start with an EEG
and some basic tests today.
Please come this way.
Okay.
-Good luck with the tests.
-Okay.
If I'd known he was coming,
I would have put in an extra insole.
Come on, Gi-jun.
You always look so handsome,
but today of all days,
why do you look so shabby?
Hold up, An Gi-jun.
Have some dignity.
You have nothing to feel small about
anymore, okay?
Jang Tae-ha is a former thug,
and you're a doctor.
You're on a different level, okay?
If Su-ji has any sense,
she won't be interested in him anymore.
Seriously, what is there to see in him?
It's been a while, Jang Tae-ha.
Don't you remember me?
We were classmates in high school.
Before you moved to Seoul.
Right.
Right!
Su…
Sun-deok?
It's Su-ji. Min Su-ji.
Right. Sorry.
Are you back in Gujin?
Yeah, I live in Taffy Village.
With your girlfriend?
Yeah.
Hey, Go Eun-sae.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. I just stubbed my toe.
-Does it hurt a lot? Can you walk?
-I'm fine.
Stop overreacting.
People would think I lost a foot.
-You should be more careful.
-Hold on.
Once we have the results,
we'll start the treatment next week.
We'll do a drug test, then begin
cognitive rehabilitation therapy.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
No need to thank me.
God bless you.
We'll get going, then.
-Okay.
-Bye, Ji-su.
It's… Su-ji.
You seem happy to see your first love.
Yeah.
It looks like Jang Tae-ha's still got it.
That woman earlier.
She was your classmate?
-Yeah.
-I see.
Well, she was… a bit pretty.
With today's beauty techniques,
almost anyone can look like her
with a little effort.
It's only because I'm wearing
these tacky clothes,
but if I dressed up, I'd be a knockout.
Should we go shopping?
There's a mall in town.
-What do you think?
-It's pretty.
-How about this one?
How about this?
It's pretty.
Stop saying "it's pretty"
without meaning it.
I do mean it.
You looked pretty in every single one.
How can you say that so casually?
It's true though.
You already put a pink one in here.
That was coral pink.
This one is bright pink.
They're different?
Of course they are.
No two shades are ever the same.
You really are clueless.
This one's moist. I like it.
And the ingredients look good too.
One of those.
I think that's enough for makeup.
You know…
There's one last thing that I need.
Now I feel like I can breathe.
A modern person needs a phone, after all.
It's a shame
that it's registered under your name,
but I guess it can't be helped.
You look happy.
Yes, today isn't so bad.
We agreed that I'd get treatment,
I got a phone,
and I went shopping.
That was such a stress reliever.
Let's see.
Huh?
I only picked up one of these.
Did you add the rest of them?
Yeah, you said it was good.
I can't believe you.
You didn't have to be so thoughtful.
I have a small face,
so one cushion foundation
lasts me a long time.
When will I use all this up?
They're not for you.
Then who are they for?
I heard this is good.
-One for each of you.
-What's this?
If I use this,
I'll really look as pretty as a new bride.
Right, honey?
Of course.
You'll be the prettiest girl in town.
Wait a minute.
One second. That's not how you use it.
I'll show you how to use it.
You only need a slight dab.
I'll put it on for you.
Like this. Just tap like this, and then…
Tap, tap.
Tap gently.
Just like this.
Your face looks brighter
just from evening out your skin tone.
Wait a minute.
Goodness me.
Why are there so many different
colored powders to put on your face?
I think this will look good on you.
One second.
-Here.
-More?
Just a little more of this.
Okay.
Wow, that's pretty.
-Let me see.
-You look so pretty.
Good heavens!
My face looks so rosy and healthy.
Isn't that right?
This looks good on you,
so I'll give it to you as a gift.
Use it from now on.
-And for you, Song-wol…
-How lovely.
This one.
Thanks for today.
For what?
For dolling Grandma up.
I never knew she was so pretty.
You really like your grandma.
Because she's my grandma.
-Hello, Coach.
-Hey, Pil-seung.
-Are you training hard?
-Yes, I am.
-Good.
-I'll be going now.
See you.
Who was that?
Ms. Pang's son. He goes to our gym.
Who's Ms. Pang?
A woman who hangs out
with the shaman lady--
You mean the S.E.S of Taffy Village?
Their leader.
That lady.
Her son is handsome.
He doesn't take after his mom at all.
Don't tell anyone in the village
that Pil-seung goes to our gym.
It's a secret.
Who would I talk to in this village?
I don't have a single friend here.
Speaking of friends, you really don't know
any of their numbers?
Wasn't there anyone I would
meet often when we lived in Seoul?
I don't know.
You didn't talk about your friends much.
But I must have had at least one friend.
Why aren't my friends looking for me?
We're closed for the…
Hello.
-Here.
-Thank you.
She didn't contact you either?
She didn't.
The last time we went shopping together,
Ji-won got a little upset with me
about something.
At first, I thought she wasn't
reaching out because she was still mad.
But even after that, I couldn't
get through to her by phone or by text.
So I was planning
to report her missing tomorrow.
She's not missing. She had applied
for a long-term leave of absence.
-Long-term leave?
-Yes.
I don't know what drove her to do that,
but if you hear from Ji-won,
please let me know.
Okay, I will.
DETECTIVE AGENCY
Yes, have you found Go Ji-won?
Thank you.
Why did you ask to meet
in a place like this?
We're not close enough
to share a meal, are we?
The longer I search,
the more I realize it's no ordinary task.
We can't report her missing,
and finding someone
through unofficial channels
is a rather discreet and important task.
This kind of thing
isn't a walk in the park.
What is it you're trying to say?
I'd like to renegotiate the down payment.
So you called me out here
to ask for more money?
For large-scale jobs,
we don't cut corners on formalities.
So committed to formalities, aren't you?
Yes.
Thank you for your work.
DETECTIVE AGENCY
BREAKFAST, LUNCH, DINNER
She took all her meds.
Like this. Just tap like this, and then…
There we go.
I told you to lie low.
Look where that got you.
She did me a favor by disappearing
voluntarily. Why try to find her?
Still,
why must you go this far…
The best way to grow an apple tree…
is to cut off the buds
that are bothersome.
"What if I let this one be?"
"What if I let it grow a little
and then cut it off?"
A moment's hesitation…
could ruin your entire harvest.
No, but…
Wait, hold on.
Wait.
Please don't kill me. Wait, please.
No, wait.
Hold on.
Please, no!
There's more than just the watch!
It's not just the watch.
There's one more thing.
Prosecutor Go said she had prepared
one more thing besides the watch.
That's what I was looking for.
If I'm alive, and if Ji-won…
I mean, if Prosecutor Go is alive,
surely I could be of use to you later on?
Please don't kill me.
What is it?
You put makeup on.
I bought so much yesterday,
so I should use it.
Don't go falling for me.
As if I could help it.
It's so good.
Oh, right.
Let's go to Seoul.
We lived there longer than here.
I might remember something
if we go back to where we lived.
We can't do that.
Why not?
You're not
fully recovered for a long trip like that.
It's not like we'd be going
to the other side of the world.
It's only a few hours away.
We don't have many good memories in Seoul.
It'll just make us feel bad.
Good or bad,
I need to find whatever memories I can--
How about a ride?
-What?
-You liked riding scooters.
I did?
Whenever you were stressed,
you'd go riding.
You should try it.
It might help you remember something.
Scooters?
Why does this feel so familiar?
Okay, let's start slow--
I know this.
Yes, I know this!
I know this, I do!
-Hold on tight.
-Careful.
I'm good at this.
No way.
This feels great!
Are they filming an action movie?
Why are they speeding around
the village on a scooter?
Exactly. Why are they speeding
when no one's even chasing them?
Leave them be.
-They're still in the honeymoon phase.
-That's the honeymoon phase?
When it looks like shenanigans
from the outside
but makes perfect sense to them.
That's dating for you.
I wouldn't know. The last time
I felt love in the air was in a past life.
Oh, enough with that.
Let's go do our hair.
-Let's go.
-Let's.
-Just one last drink.
-Yes.
Cheers!
Awesome!
This is so cool.
Why am I so good at riding a scooter?
You said you'd done courier work.
I did?
Remember anything?
I don't.
But I can tell
I was good at riding scooters.
My body remembers.
What else did I like?
What?
Tell me more. I want to keep finding out.
Taking pictures.
Pictures?
How do I look?
Come on, it looks like I'm planted there.
What's with these proportions?
My legs look so short!
Look closely.
Take it so that my feet are one centimeter
above the bottom of the screen.
That way, my legs will look longer.
How do I know these details?
I told you that you liked taking pictures.
Anyway, take it again. One centimeter!
Well, that's a new level of ridiculous.
Will it kill her to look at the camera?
She's dead set on avoiding the camera.
When did he become
such a hopeless romantic?
He'll do whatever his wife asks him to do.
-Why do we even bother?
-Such an eyesore.
Let's go.
Some of these
might actually be worth keeping.
But I really don't remember any of this.
Seeing how at ease I was and how much fun
I had in front of the camera,
I think I really liked this too.
Did I use any social media by any chance?
If I liked taking pictures so much,
I might have posted them somewhere.
I've already searched for Go Eun-sae
on all the social media platforms,
but I haven't found my account yet.
I'm not sure. I don't think you did.
What about my usual username?
I don't know.
See? This is the kind of thing
that makes me distrust you.
How could you not know
your girlfriend's usual username?
Even if you really are my boyfriend,
I'm disappointed.
Why'd I date such an indifferent guy?
We tried a lot of things,
but I still couldn't remember anything.
It was totally unproductive.
Speaking of productivity,
why do you keep following me around?
Aren't you going to the gym to work?
This is a special situation,
so Mr. Hong understands.
No way.
You must be crazy!
If you just hang around like this at home,
who's going to pay the bills?
I can't exactly go out and work right now.
How are you going to support me?
Ask all the village ladies and see
if any woman would be okay
with her perfectly healthy husband
sitting around at home.
I thought--
There's nothing more for me
to be curious about or find unfamiliar
in this tiny village.
So go out
and work.
Men look their best when they're working.
Later, I'm going to help Pil-seung
for a bit with his sparring.
I won't let you go hungry.
Were you even listening?
You're going to go out for a bit
and then come back home?
I'm so sick of this.
Completely sick of this.
How will we afford our beef?
I want to eat beef.
I'd better go make money.
We heard about your date today.
-What?
-The whole village knows.
That the two of you were like a scene
from a romantic movie.
We just rode a scooter for a bit
to see if it would jog her memory.
-And we took some pictures.
-Right.
We were thirsty,
so we bought some drinks. That's all.
That's what we call a date, buddy.
I heard you were lying flat on the ground
just to take her picture!
She kept saying they looked weird
and made me retake them.
They all looked good and pretty to me.
She looked pretty no matter the shot.
Even the pictures she deleted,
saying they looked bad, were pretty.
She kept denying it.
Tae-ha.
Yes, sir?
Sorry about everything.
What?
So this is what it feels like
to have a mirror held up to you.
Why are you going to a PC café
three days in a row?
He's adorable.
What's going to become of you
if you keep playing computer games?
Hey, Geum-hyang.
The idea that video games ruin your life
is old news.
These days, you can earn millions
playing computer games.
If he's not good at studying,
it might be better to get into gaming.
I'm fully supporting
Pil-seung's gaming career.
You even have to support him?
He's already given up on studying.
It's admirable that he's working so hard
on something.
As expected,
you're so open-minded, Hui-ja.
My darling Jun-sik,
cute like the meaty part of a mackerel.
Don't bother.
This 10,000 won is for you.
Thank you.
And Pil-seung is at the PC café, right?
Take this 10,000-won note to Pil-seung.
Pil-seung isn't there.
He's not? What do you mean?
He always goes to the PC café after school
to play computer games.
No, he doesn't.
He wasn't there yesterday
or the day before.
Then where does he go?
Is anything fun on?
…the ceremony for the Irang-dong
development project
was attended by Gangju City officials
and Mirae Eden Company representatives…
They both look so shady.
Their faces really rub me the wrong way.
TOP 3 OMAKASE RESTAURANTS IN SEOUL
Goodness.
What is that? It looks delicious.
Wow.
Look at how shiny the tuna is.
It's totally my thing.
It'd be perfect
if I could eat there right now.
The Cheongdam
Class.
The vibe is amazing.
The people who get to eat here
are so lucky.
I bet it'd be a great spot for photos.
This is
me.
Bestie?
A FEAST WITH MY BESTIE
My friend?
GO JI-WON, PARK HYO-JIN
FOUND A MEMORY WITH JI-WON
It's me.
Yes, this is me.
But why does it say "Go Ji-won"
under my photo?
Is my name… Go ji-won?
Go Eun-sae.
They're not here.
They aren't here.
The clothes, this bag, the ring.
Everything in these photos…
None of it's here.
You hated superficial things.
It wasn't true.
None of it was true.
HONG'S BOXING GYM
I can't believe you, Tae-ha. And Mr. Hong!
As adults, how could you just
watch a kid lie and do nothing?
Pil-seung really loves boxing.
And he's good at it.
Save it! So what if he's good?
He'll just end up like you, a thug.
You showed us that yourself.
You even made the national team,
and you still ended up a gangster.
You think I want to see
my son end up like that?
A gangster?
Jang Tae-ha was a gangster?
OUR STICKY LOVE
Subtitle translation by: Jimin Choi